we're asked to use the array each method
to iterate over an array of integers
from 1 to 10
and print each value so let's just
initialize an array here
so on line one we have an array of
integers one to ten
and now we want to invoke the array each
method on this array
we know that each element of this array
is going to be passed as an
argument to the block so let's call that
block parameter
number
now within the block we simply need to
output
each value and we can do that by
invoking put us
now when we run our code we expect to
see each number from 1
through 10 output on its own line
and that's what we see
now because the code within our block
here is so short we can actually
write our block on only one line
here rather than using do and end
to start and end our block we use curly
braces
this code is still pretty easy to read
and when we run it
we see the same output